<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Hey Mom, I&#39;m learning new things!</title>
    <link>https://blog.placerda.pt/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Hey Mom, I&#39;m learning new things!</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <managingEditor>antonioplacerda@gmail.com (Antonio P. Lacerda)</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>antonioplacerda@gmail.com (Antonio P. Lacerda)</webMaster>
    <copyright>Everything is mine</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 24 Oct 2019 22:24:31 +0100</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://blog.placerda.pt/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Docker Commands</title>
      <link>https://blog.placerda.pt/code/snippets/20191024-docker-commands/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Oct 2019 22:24:31 +0100</pubDate>
      <author>antonioplacerda@gmail.com (Antonio P. Lacerda)</author>
      <guid>https://blog.placerda.pt/code/snippets/20191024-docker-commands/</guid>
      <description>This is a list of every docker command I find useful and a bit of info about it. It is not intended to be a tutorial of any kind, but maybe someone will find this list as useful as I consider it to be!
General  docker version - if any error here, docker is probably not running. If on linux, do a sudo docker info - a lot more info about the docker installation  Containers  docker container run IMAGE - first it gets an image from local machine, if it doesn’t find one, tries to get one from docker hub.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Remove Diacritics</title>
      <link>https://blog.placerda.pt/code/snippets/20190706-diacritics/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 06 Jul 2019 09:45:53 +0100</pubDate>
      <author>antonioplacerda@gmail.com (Antonio P. Lacerda)</author>
      <guid>https://blog.placerda.pt/code/snippets/20190706-diacritics/</guid>
      <description>If you ever faced the terror of finding a diacritic that messed up some of your regex, or some awesome script you&amp;rsquo;ve written, then we are on the same boat. Although I love my language, portuguese, messing up with scripts is never a good way to make friends, so I often need to remove those annoying characters from sentences and every time I need to do so I go surf the web for the same answer.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hello, World</title>
      <link>https://blog.placerda.pt/post/20181016-hello/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Oct 2018 05:53:52 +0100</pubDate>
      <author>antonioplacerda@gmail.com (Antonio P. Lacerda)</author>
      <guid>https://blog.placerda.pt/post/20181016-hello/</guid>
      <description>This is my first post. This is the beginning of something amazing. I&amp;rsquo;ve been wanting to give back to the community for a long time but didn&amp;rsquo;t know how to. Well, this is how I plan to start! I want to have a place where I put everything I learn, that is accessible everywhere and to everyone. No better place than here. I also wanted to create something hackable but not fully from scratch, since it would take longer than I&amp;rsquo;d like.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About me</title>
      <link>https://blog.placerda.pt/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>antonioplacerda@gmail.com (Antonio P. Lacerda)</author>
      <guid>https://blog.placerda.pt/about/</guid>
      <description>My name is Antonio, I am catholic, a developer and a black belt in taekwondo. I have a general interest in everything about tech and I am obsessed with productivity.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>