<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on antonio p lacerda</title>
    <link>https://antonioplacerda.github.io/posts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on antonio p lacerda</description>
    <image>
      <url>https://antonioplacerda.github.io/papermod-cover.png</url>
      <link>https://antonioplacerda.github.io/papermod-cover.png</link>
    </image>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 15 Jul 2021 00:08:43 +0100</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://antonioplacerda.github.io/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Creating my first DApp</title>
      <link>https://antonioplacerda.github.io/posts/20210714_first_dapp/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jul 2021 00:08:43 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://antonioplacerda.github.io/posts/20210714_first_dapp/</guid>
      <description>It&amp;rsquo;s time to get my Q3 goals going and I&amp;rsquo;ve decided to go with the DApp!
I will do this in 4 steps:
 Create a lottery contract using the remix platform; Create a frontend to interact with the contract, that should be connected to metamask; Deploy the contract to a testnet like Rinkeby; Maybe deploy the app to heroku.  So, the contract should be able to:
 Allow players to enter the lottery with a fixed amount of ether, like 0.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2021 Q3 Goals</title>
      <link>https://antonioplacerda.github.io/posts/20210713_q3goals/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Jul 2021 23:54:17 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://antonioplacerda.github.io/posts/20210713_q3goals/</guid>
      <description>OK, now it&amp;rsquo;s time to define some priorities. Having dreams is great, but that doesn&amp;rsquo;t get anything done. And also, having them in kind of a blob is also no good!
I know I want to improve my technical skills to feel more comfortable taking on any new challenge that I might face. I know I want to learn more about blockchains and smart contracts. I know I want to improve my trading skills.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2021 Dreams</title>
      <link>https://antonioplacerda.github.io/posts/20210712_2021dreams/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jul 2021 08:16:45 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://antonioplacerda.github.io/posts/20210712_2021dreams/</guid>
      <description>A full year is too long to set goals. It&amp;rsquo;s a bettter timespan to set dreams, that will get translated into goals for each quarter, that should get translated into projects and then into concrete small actions. I will try to do that, since I&amp;rsquo;ve spent these past quarters dreaming about these goals!
But, for now, here are my dreams for 2021:
 Create a simple DCA trading bot for DeFi; Start a &amp;ldquo;strategy&amp;rdquo; journal, where I will implement several trading strategies and backtest them; Improve my algorithms and data structures knowledge; Improve my system design skills; Improve my pattern recognition for trading skills; Create a simple DApp in the ethereum blockchain; Create a bot to automatically claim rewards from farms and swap them; Create an explorer sniffer, that will fetch all transactions for the supplied address; Create a portfolio app, that will get the records from several exchanges; Add the explorer info to the portfolio app; Create an arbitrageur bot for CEX; Create an arbitrageur bot for DEX; Improve my go skills;  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Docker Commands</title>
      <link>https://antonioplacerda.github.io/posts/20191024-docker-commands/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Oct 2019 22:24:31 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://antonioplacerda.github.io/posts/20191024-docker-commands/</guid>
      <description>This is a list of every docker command I find useful and a bit of info about it. It is not intended to be a tutorial of any kind, but maybe someone will find this list as useful as I consider it to be!
General  docker version - if any error here, docker is probably not running. If on linux, do a sudo docker info - a lot more info about the docker installation  Containers  docker container run IMAGE - first it gets an image from local machine, if it doesn’t find one, tries to get one from docker hub.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Remove Diacritics</title>
      <link>https://antonioplacerda.github.io/posts/20190706-diacritics/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 06 Jul 2019 09:45:53 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://antonioplacerda.github.io/posts/20190706-diacritics/</guid>
      <description>If you ever faced the terror of finding a diacritic that messed up some of your regex, or some awesome script you&amp;rsquo;ve written, then we are on the same boat. Although I love my language, portuguese, messing up with scripts is never a good way to make friends, so I often need to remove those annoying characters from sentences and every time I need to do so I go surf the web for the same answer.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hello, World</title>
      <link>https://antonioplacerda.github.io/posts/20181016-hello/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Oct 2018 05:53:52 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://antonioplacerda.github.io/posts/20181016-hello/</guid>
      <description>This is my first post. This is the beginning of something amazing, I hope. I&amp;rsquo;ve been wanting to give back to the community for a long time but didn&amp;rsquo;t know how to. Well, this is how I plan to start! I want to have a place where I put everything I learn, that is accessible everywhere and to everyone. No better place than here. I also wanted to create something hackable but not fully from scratch, since it would take longer than I&amp;rsquo;d like.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
